[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was rock singer Pink born?", "correct_answer": "1979", "incorrect_answers": ["1983", "1969", "1971"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oregano is a spicy perennial herb, particularly common to which region in Europe?", "correct_answer": "The Mediterranean Region", "incorrect_answers": ["The Baltic Region", "The North Region", "The Arabic Region"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The S.O.S. on SOS cleaning pads stands for Save Our Saucepans.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Latin prefix homo refer to?", "correct_answer": "Mankind", "incorrect_answers": ["Sameness", "Study of", "Science"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this drama film by Bernardo Bertolucci, a couple journey to northern Africa to rekindle their marriage.", "correct_answer": "The Sheltering Sky", "incorrect_answers": ["La Luna", "The Conformist", "La commare secca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie Adventures in Babysitting premiere?", "correct_answer": "1987", "incorrect_answers": ["1985", "1986", "1988"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Benny Goodman, a great clarinetist, was always compared to this great jazz clarinetist, composer, bandleader, and writer.", "correct_answer": "Artie Shaw", "incorrect_answers": ["Cootie Williams", "Art Farmer", "Bunny Berrigan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of guy is Gerard Butlers character in The Ugly Truth movie?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Overconfident", "Cynical", "Male chauvinist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the zoo in which the last known Thylacine was placed in 1936?", "correct_answer": "Hobart Zoo", "incorrect_answers": ["Queensland Zoo", "Queen Elizabeth Zoological Gardens", "Australia Zoo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies did not involve Roberto Benigni?", "correct_answer": "Playtime", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny Stecchino", "The Monster", "Life is Beautiful (Vita \u00e8 bella, La)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When does Dr. Bruce Banner transform into Hulk in one of the most expensive films in history, The Incredible Hulk (2008)?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["When he is angry", "When he is exited", "When he is stressed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of dessert is the Boston cream pie?", "correct_answer": "Cake", "incorrect_answers": ["Ice cream", "Tortellini", "Biscuit"]}]